You never got the point of these.
To me, they always looked like granddad's bollocks flopping in the window.
Don't give a mother effing doodle how he checked out.
Ah, bollocks.
He didn't die like no hero.
I'll wager he went out on his knees begging like a right
cunt.
What the f...
Sorry, love.
Next.
Number one.
Uh-uh.
Sorry, mate.
There you go.
Nice piece.
Welcome.
Next.
Speaking of which, I haven't seen Translucent around anywhere.
You wouldn't happen to know anything about that, would you?
Cunt's invisible.
He could be standing in that f... corner, plugging one out right
now for all we know.
You can't even give me this, can you?
Not one goddamn win.
I'll tell you what.
When we're all done here, I'll buy you a nice big family-sized
bottle of top-shelf lube.
And I'll tickle your balls till your big meat is stoned.
I almost forgot.
I got you something.
Terror?
Fuck it.
That's my boy.
Gift-wrapping it as polio vaccine.
Are you telling me that God's not reaching up the twats of
American girls and blessing babies?
Butcher, can you leave God out of this?
Now, it's completely harmless to humans, but to soups.
Fuckin' diabolical.
Peel back the plastic bit to reveal the sticky side.
Put the plastic bit in the bog.
Flush it.
Then go back into the boardroom.
Sit down.
Big smiles.
Plant the bug underneath the table.
Easy peasy.
Japanese-y.
Bob's your uncle.
It could be anything.
You don't trust me.
Susan, I am shocked and saddened by that.
Attack us, okay?
And you're a federal officer, you know?
Just call the fucking FBI.
Yeah, okay, so look.
Technically, I'm not a fed.
What?!
Of this shit, and to me and Kimiko, and we just...
Drop dead?
Yep.
That's the idea.
Hey.
Helping him on his missions.
Letting him watch you on the bog.
Stick his finger up your bum a bit.
Give him a sloppy little nosh.
All in a day's work for you.
I'll miss us.
Bloody hell.
You wait to your own voice, don't ya?
Gentlemen.
I have pottery class in ten minutes.
Right.
Would you rather finger some fucking clay,
Or...
Walk the fuck out of here.
Fuck, well, you're a grateful cunt, aren't you?
Where's your fucking men?
Don't care who you just throw to the wolves?
No.
Not really.
You're a monster, and I'm not letting you do this.
Oh, what?
You're gonna go stark raving like you did with Firecracker?
I got the head popper, and you can't even get out!
Enough!
Huey, calm down, alright?
This is like that scene in The Matrix.
Now, you could take the fucking red pill, right?